heyshrav@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/heyshrav

+91-9740 269570



BS Shravan

ABOUT

Senior Undergrad Student at Global Academy of Technology, Bengaluru.

Working as a Freelance UI Designer & Web Designer for the past 1-2 years and carry an experience of working Interning for two startups.

I am also passionate about Photography and keep a good amount of interest in Product Management.

SKILLS

Visual Design
Rapid Prototyping
Creative Thinking
Design Research
Wireframing
Leadership
Project Management
Team Management
Public Speaking

TOOLS

DESIGN

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Marvel

Zeplin

Adobe Premiere Pro

Protopie & Framer

TECHNICAL

HTML5 CSS3 LESS/SCSS
Bootstrap REACT.js
MySQL Java AWS (basics)
Azure (basics) WordPress

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Kannada

EXPERIENCE

User Interface Designer

Klapklap

Jun 2020 - Jul 2020 (2 months)

Worked as a Lead UI Design Intern for Klapklap where my main focus of work included:

- Conceptualizing the UI for main app (iOS & Android)
- Improving User Experience
- Providing the required graphics assets.
- · Gamification for audience building

Graphic Design Intern

Coinmaniacs

May 2020 - Sept 2020 (5 months)

Worked as a Head of Design Intern for Coinmaniacs where my main focus of work included:

- Social Media Content Creation
- Improving User Experience on the website
- Providing the required graphical assets to the team.
- Creating audience driven graphic content.

EDUCATION

Global Academy Of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2017 - 2021

Maharishi Vidya Mandir Sr. Secondary School

School, PCM + Information Practices 2005 - 2017

ACHIEVEMENTS

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador

Microsoft

Learn Student Ambassadors are a global group of campus leaders who are eager to help fellow students, create robust tech communities and develop technical and career skills for the future.

Featured Photographer on @NatGeoIndia

National Geographic India